Faculty Reference; Collection ua950.003
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- H, 1851-2005; 8
  - Hitchcock, Karen R., Undated (Box 18, Folder 60)
  - Hitchcock, Karen R., Undated (Box 18, Folder 61)
  - Hitchcock, Karen R., Undated (Box 18, Folder 62)
  - Hitchcock, Karen, 1996 April 24 (Box 18, Folder 63)
  - Hitchcock, Karen, Undated (Box 18, Folder 64)
  - Ho, Paul, Undated (Box 18, Folder 65)
  - Hoagland, John S., Undated (Box 18, Folder 66)
  - Hobbs, Gary W., Undated (Box 18, Folder 67)
  - Hodge, Francis P., Undated (Box 18, Folder 68)
  - Hodge, Frank, Undated (Box 18, Folder 69)
  - Hodges, Stephen, Undated (Box 18, Folder 70)
  - Hoecker, Denise K., Undated (Box 18, Folder 71)
  - Hoehn, Nancy M., Undated (Box 18, Folder 72)
  - Hoff, Timothy J., Undated (Box 18, Folder 73)
  - Hoffmann, Erik P, Undated (Box 18, Folder 74)
  - Hoffmann, Erik P, Undated (Box 18, Folder 75)
  - Hoffman, Richard J., 1998-2001 (Box 18, Folder 76)
  - Hoffman, Robert, Undated (Box 18, Folder 77)
  - Hoffman, Robert, Undated (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Hogan, Austin W., Undated (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Hogan, Austin, ca. 1966-1987 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Hogan, Justin, Undated (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Hogan, Paul, Undated (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Holler, Leslie Ann, Undated (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Hollon, Robert E., Undated (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Holmes, David, Undated (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Holsinger, Donald B., Undated (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Holstein, William K., Undated (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Holstein, William K., Undated (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Holstein, William K., Undated (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Holstein, William K., Undated (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Holstein, William K., Undated (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Holt, Linda, Undated (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Hood, Janet, Undated (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Hood, Janet, Undated (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Hoogenboom, Hilde, Undated (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Hoover, Robert C., Undated (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Hope, Monica, Undated (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Hopkins, Vivian C., 1909-1990 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Hopkins, Vivian, Undated (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Hopson, Laura, Undated (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Horgen, Anne, Undated (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Horn, Margarite E., 1997 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Horne, Marcia, Undated (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Horner, Harlan Hoy, 1917-1923 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Horney, Julie, Undated (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Horney, Julie, Undated (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Horowitz, Mrs. Bernard (Helen), Undated (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Horowitz, Helen G., Undated (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - Horton, Heather K., Undated (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - Hoskins, Ronald B, Undated (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - Hotaling, Kay C., Undated (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - Hotchkiss, Rollin, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 35)
  - Hotelling, Charles S., Undated (Box 19, Folder 36)
  - Hotopp, Matt, Undated (Box 19, Folder 37)
  - Houschen, Ellen, Undated (Box 19, Folder 38)
  - Howard, Carl L., Undated (Box 19, Folder 39)
  - Howard, Carolyn, Undated (Box 19, Folder 40)
  - Howell, Robert, Undated (Box 19, Folder 41)
  - Howell, Robert C., Undated (Box 19, Folder 42)
  - Howes, Harold, Undated (Box 19, Folder 43)
  - Howes, Harold, Undated (Box 19, Folder 44)
  - Hoyle, Norman, Undated (Box 19, Folder 45)
  - Hu, Zheng, Undated (Box 19, Folder 46)
  - Huang, Mengbing, Undated (Box 19, Folder 47)
  - Huang, Youquin, Undated (Box 19, Folder 48)
  - Hudson, Cheryl, Undated (Box 19, Folder 49)
  - Hudson, Judith, Undated (Box 19, Folder 50)
  - Hudson, Judith, Undated (Box 19, Folder 51)
  - Huffmire, Margaret Conway, Undated (Box 19, Folder 52)
  - Hughes, James W., Undated (Box 19, Folder 53)
  - Hughes, Susan M., Undated (Box 19, Folder 54)
  - Hughs, Richard E., Undated (Box 19, Folder 55)
  - Hulstrunk, A., Undated (Box 19, Folder 56)
  - Humphrey, Alex, Undated (Box 19, Folder 57)
  - Humphries, Laud, Undated (Box 19, Folder 58)
  - Hunsberger, I. Moyer, Undated (Box 19, Folder 59)
  - Hunter, Gregory Scott, Undated (Box 19, Folder 60)
  - Hunt, Harry B. III, Undated (Box 19, Folder 61)
  - Hunt, Patrick J., Undated (Box 19, Folder 62)
  - Hurley, Ivan, Undated (Box 19, Folder 63)
  - Hurst, Vernon T., Undated (Box 19, Folder 64)
  - Husson, William, Undated (Box 19, Folder 65)
  - Hutchins, Ruth E., Undated (Box 19, Folder 66)
  - Hutchinson, David, Undated (Box 19, Folder 67)
  - Huth, Harvey, Undated (Box 19, Folder 68)
  - Huxford, Kathryn, Undated (Box 19, Folder 69)
  - Hwang, Syni-An, Undated (Box 19, Folder 70)
  - Hyde, Jonathan, Undated (Box 19, Folder 71)
- I, 1851-2005; 9
  - Iacobucci, Christine, Undated (Box 19, Folder 72)
  - Idleman, Peter, Undated (Box 19, Folder 73)
  - Idone, Vincent, Undated (Box 19, Folder 74)
  - Ilchman, Warren F., Undated (Box 19, Folder 75)
  - Ilchman, Warren F., Undated (Box 19, Folder 76)
  - Infante, Dominic A., Undated (Box 19, Folder 77)
  - Ingison, Linda J., 1980 (Box 19, Folder 78)
  - Ingles, Richard, Undated (Box 19, Folder 79)
  - Inomata, Akira, Undated (Box 19, Folder 80)
  - Inomata, Akira, Undated (Box 19, Folder 81)
  - Ireland, Timothy, Undated (Box 19, Folder 82)
  - Irving, Suzanne, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 83)
  - Israel, Allen C., Undated (Box 19, Folder 84)
  - Isser, Stanley J., Undated (Box 19, Folder 85)
  - Istvan, Joseph A., Undated (Box 19, Folder 86)
  - Ivanoff, Andre M., Undated (Box 19, Folder 87)
  - Ives, Jane K., Undated (Box 19, Folder 88)
  - Iwanska, Alicja, Undated (Box 19, Folder 89)
  - Iwanska, Alicja, Undated (Box 19, Folder 90)
  - Izzard, Colin S., Undated (Box 19, Folder 91)
- J, 1851-2005; 10
  - Jaccard, James J., Undated (Box 19, Folder 92)
  - Jaccard, James, Undated (Box 19, Folder 93)
  - Jacklet, Alice, Undated (Box 19, Folder 94)
  - Jacklet, Jon W., Undated (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Jacklet, Jon W., Undated (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Jacobi, Lotte, Undated (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Jacobs, Suzanne, Undated (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Jacobs, Ronald, Undated (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Jacobson, Dorothy T., Undated (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Jacobson, Dorothy, Undated (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Jacobson, Trudi, Undated (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Jaeger, Robert G., Undated (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Jagerson, Todd, Undated (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - James, Jasmine, Undated (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Jamison, Benton N., Undated (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Jamison, Benton, Undated (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Janecek, John, Undated (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Janesick, Valerie J., Undated (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Jelinek, Mariann, Undated (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Janower, David M., Undated (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Jarvenpa, Robert, Undated (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Jarvis, Dave, Undated (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Jean-Baptiste, Rachel, Undated (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Jefferson, Roslyn, Undated (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Jeffries, Leonard, Undated (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Jenkins, Joe W., Undated (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Jenkins, Joe W., Undated (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Jenks, David W., Undated (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Jennings, Edward M., Undated (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Jennings, Edward M., Undated (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Jennings, John W., Undated (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - Jerison, Michael, Undated (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - Jerison, Michael, Undated (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - Jerum, Kathryn J., Undated (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - Jewett, Alice B., Undated (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - Jiusto, James E., Undated (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - Jiusto, James, Undated (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - Johnpoll, Bernard K., Undated (Box 20, Folder 35)
  - Johnpoll, Bernard K., Undated (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - Johnson, Jacqueline, Undated (Box 20, Folder 37)
  - Johnson, Judith, Undated (Box 20, Folder 38)
  - Johnson, Kecia, Undated (Box 20, Folder 39)
  - Johnson, Mauritz, 1955-1968 (Box 20, Folder 40)
  - Johnson, Mauritz, Jr., Undated (Box 20, Folder 41)
  - Johnson, Mary T., Undated (Box 20, Folder 42)
  - Johnson, Pamela F., Undated (Box 20, Folder 43)
  - Johnson, Robin Mackenzie, Undated (Box 20, Folder 44)
  - Johnson, Sally, Undated (Box 20, Folder 45)
  - Johnston, Peter H., Undated (Box 20, Folder 46)
  - Johnstone, Bruce, Undated (Box 20, Folder 47)
  - Johnstone, Bruce D., Undated (Box 20, Folder 48)
  - Jones, Alethia, Undated (Box 20, Folder 49)
  - Jones, Christopher C., Undated (Box 20, Folder 50)
  - Jones, Gary L., Undated (Box 20, Folder 51)
  - Jones, Gary L., Undated (Box 20, Folder 52)
  - Jones, Jacquelyn, Undated (Box 20, Folder 53)
  - Jones, Jeffrey J., Undated (Box 20, Folder 54)
  - Jones, Jennifer, Undated (Box 20, Folder 55)
  - Jones, Kenneth, Undated (Box 20, Folder 56)
  - Jones, Shirley, Undated (Box 20, Folder 57)
  - Jones, Shirley, Undated (Box 20, Folder 58)
  - Jordan, Bojana Vuyisile, Undated (Box 20, Folder 59)
  - Jorden, Frederick E., Undated (Box 20, Folder 60)
  - Jordon, Lucious, Undated (Box 20, Folder 61)
  - Jorgensen, June, Undated (Box 20, Folder 62)
  - Joris, Pierre, Undated (Box 20, Folder 63)
  - Joseph, Deborah, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 64)
  - Josey, E.J., Undated (Box 20, Folder 65)
  - Juedes, Donald R., 1994-1998 (Box 20, Folder 66)
  - Jumpeter, Christine E., Undated (Box 20, Folder 67)
  - Juncker, Paul, Undated (Box 20, Folder 68)
  - Jurkowski, Janine M, Undated (Box 20, Folder 69)
  - Jury, Mark, Undated (Box 20, Folder 70)
  - Justeson, John, Undated (Box 20, Folder 71)
- K, 1851-2005; 11
  - Kaczor, Sue A., Undated (Box 20, Folder 72)
  - Kadlecek, John, Undated (Box 20, Folder 73)
  - Kadlecek, John A., Undated (Box 20, Folder 74)
  - Kagan, Richard M., Undated (Box 20, Folder 75)
  - Kahalas, Harvey, Undated (Box 20, Folder 76)
  - Kakumba, Dawn V., Undated (Box 20, Folder 77)
  - Kalish, Richard Jerome, Undated (Box 20, Folder 78)
  - Kallman, Howard J., Undated (Box 20, Folder 79)
  - Kaloyeros, Alain, Undated (Box 20, Folder 80)
  - Kaloyeros, Alain, Undated (Box 20, Folder 81)
  - Kaloyeros, Alain, Undated (Box 20, Folder 82)
  - Kaloyeros, Alain, Undated (Box 20, Folder 83)
  - Kaloyeros, Alain, Undated (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Kamberelis, George, Undated (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Kanes, Martin, Undated (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Kane, Shirley, Undated (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Kane, Shirley M., Undated (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Kaneko, Motohisa, Undated (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Kapechuk, Walter, Undated (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Garcia-Kapelewski, Martha, Undated (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Kanes, Martin, Undated (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Kapur, Deepak, Undated (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Karageorghia, Vassos, Undated (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Karlin, Kenneth D., Undated (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Karlson, Karleen, Undated (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Karpel, Leon, Undated (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Karpinski, Jakub, Undated (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Karsick, Margaret Barnes, Undated (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Karson, William, Undated (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Karuzan, O. Charles, Undated (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Kashiwase, Yasuji, Undated (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Kastle, Leonard, Undated (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Katagiri, Catharine M., Undated (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Katz, Daniel J., Undated (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Katz, Linda S., Undated (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Katz, Linda Steinberg, Undated (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Katz, Melvin L., Undated (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Katz, Melvin, Undated (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Katz, Selig H., Undated (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - Katz, Sydney S., Undated (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - Katz, William, Undated (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - Katz, William A., Undated (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - Kaufer, David S., Undated (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - Kavanagh, Michael, Undated (Box 21, Folder 32)
  - Kavanagh, Michael J., Undated (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - Kazmierski, Georgiana M., Undated (Box 21, Folder 34)
  - Kehe, Zhu, Undated (Box 21, Folder 35)
  - Kekes, John, Undated (Box 21, Folder 36)
  - Keller, Kevin E., Undated (Box 21, Folder 37)
  - Keller, William E., Undated (Box 21, Folder 38)
  - Kelley, Kathryn, Undated (Box 21, Folder 39)
  - Kellner, Menachem, Undated (Box 21, Folder 40)
  - Kellogg, Ruth, Undated (Box 21, Folder 41)
  - Kelly, Brian V., Undated (Box 21, Folder 42)
  - Kelly, Edward F., Undated (Box 21, Folder 43)
  - Kelly, James F., Undated (Box 21, Folder 44)
  - Kelly, Piret K, Undated (Box 21, Folder 45)
  - Kelly, Richard, Undated (Box 21, Folder 46)
  - Kelly, Richard, Undated (Box 21, Folder 47)
  - Kelly, Thomas G., Undated (Box 21, Folder 48)
  - Kelly, Thomas, Undated (Box 21, Folder 49)
  - Kelsey, Jean, Undated (Box 21, Folder 50)
  - Kemmerer, Frances, Undated (Box 21, Folder 51)
  - Kemmerer, Frances, Undated (Box 21, Folder 52)
  - Kemp, Barbara, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 53)
  - Kendall, Kathleen A., Undated (Box 21, Folder 54)
  - Kendall, Kathleen E., Undated (Box 21, Folder 55)
  - Kendall, Richard, Undated (Box 21, Folder 56)
  - Kendall, Richard H., Undated (Box 21, Folder 57)
  - Kendra, Christopher - French Department Faculty 1964-1969, Undated (Box 21, Folder 58)
  - Kennedy, William, Undated (Box 21, Folder 59)
  - Kennedy, William, Undated (Box 21, Folder 60)
  - Kennedy, William, Undated (Box 21, Folder 61)
  - Kennedy, William, Undated (Box 21, Folder 62)
  - Kennedy, William, Undated (Box 21, Folder 63)
  - Kenney, Ralph B., Undated (Box 21, Folder 64)
  - Kenny, David George, Undated (Box 21, Folder 65)
  - Keogan, Shonna, Undated (Box 21, Folder 66)
  - Keohane, John J., Undated (Box 21, Folder 67)
  - Keough, Brian, Undated (Box 21, Folder 68)
  - Keough, Brian, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 69)
  - Keough, Brian, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 70)
  - Kern, Douglas, Undated (Box 21, Folder 71)
  - Kersten, Christian, Undated (Box 21, Folder 72)
  - Kessler, Jane, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 73)
  - Kessler, Martin, Undated (Box 21, Folder 74)
  - Ketterer, James, Undated (Box 21, Folder 75)
  - Kettlewell, Karen, Undated (Box 21, Folder 76)
  - Keyomarsi, Khandan, Undated (Box 21, Folder 77)
  - Keys, Raymond, Undated (Box 21, Folder 78)
  - Keyser, Daniel, Undated (Box 21, Folder 79)
  - Khwaja, Haider, Undated (Box 21, Folder 80)
  - Kidder, Amy Friedman, Undated (Box 21, Folder 81)
  - Kielt, James P., Undated (Box 21, Folder 82)
  - Kiepper, James J., Undated (Box 21, Folder 83)
  - Kiepper, James J., 1964-1992 (Box 21, Folder 84)
  - Kifer, Allan, Undated (Box 21, Folder 85)
  - Kikuchi, Akio (visiting 1968-69), Undated (Box 21, Folder 86)
  - Kilcullen, Thomas F., Undated (Box 21, Folder 87)
  - Kim, Jai S., Undated (Box 21, Folder 88)
  - Kim, Jai Soo, Undated (Box 21, Folder 89)
  - Kim, Sung Bok, Undated (Box 21, Folder 90)
  - Kim, Sung Bok, Undated (Box 21, Folder 91)
  - Kim, Sung Bok, Undated (Box 21, Folder 92)
  - Kim, Sung Bok, Undated (Box 21, Folder 93)
  - Kim, Yong Moo, Undated (Box 21, Folder 94)
  - Kimball, John, Undated (Box 21, Folder 95)
  - Kimball, Kenneth R., Jr., Undated (Box 21, Folder 96)
  - Kinal, Terrence W., Undated (Box 21, Folder 97)
  - Kinard, Elissa, Undated (Box 21, Folder 98)
  - Kincaid, Lawrence, Undated (Box 21, Folder 99)
  - King, Carolyn, Undated (Box 21, Folder 100)
  - King, James, Undated (Box 21, Folder 101)
  - King, Jonathan, Undated (Box 21, Folder 102)
  - King, Robert (chancellor), Undated (Box 21, Folder 103)
  - King, Ryan D., Undated (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - King, Tsoo E., Undated (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - King, Tsoo E., Undated (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - King, Tsoo E., Undated (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Kingma, Bruce, Undated (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Kinney, Thomas, Undated (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Kinney, Thomas, Undated (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Kirk, Russell, Undated (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Kirk, Stuart A., Undated (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Kirwin, Arthur Jr., Undated (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Kivlen, Chris, Undated (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Kisseleff, Natalia, Undated (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Kizenko, Nadiezda, Undated (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Klages, Roy Arthur, Undated (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Klein, Alan F., Undated (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Klein, Alan F., Undated (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Klempner, Irving M., Undated (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Klempner, Irving M., Undated (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Kleppel, Gary, Undated (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Kleppel, Gary, Undated (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Klima, George, Undated (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Klima, George J., Undated (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Kline, David, Undated (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Klopott, R. Beth, Undated (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Klor De Alva, J. Jorge, Undated (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Knapp, Sara D., Undated (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - Knapp, Sarah, Undated (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - Knee, Michael J., Undated (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - Knight, Christopher J., Undated (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - Knight-Thomas, Dawn, Undated (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - Knoblaugh, Cyril H., Undated (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - Knoff, Howard M., Undated (Box 22, Folder 32)
  - Knotts, Walter E., Undated (Box 22, Folder 33)
  - Knotts, Walter E., Undated (Box 22, Folder 34)
  - Knouse, Reno, Undated (Box 22, Folder 35)
  - Knuth, Kevin, Undated (Box 22, Folder 36)
  - Ko, Hai-Ping, Undated (Box 22, Folder 37)
  - Koban, Charles, Undated (Box 22, Folder 38)
  - Kobrin, David, Undated (Box 22, Folder 39)
  - Koelmel, John (Jack), Undated (Box 22, Folder 40)
  - Koerner, Charlotte W., 1980 (Box 22, Folder 41)
  - Koff, Robert H., Undated (Box 22, Folder 42)
  - Kolb, Lawrence, Undated (Box 22, Folder 43)
  - Kolesoff, Valerian F., Undated (Box 22, Folder 44)
  - Kolmin, Frank W., Undated (Box 22, Folder 45)
  - Komisar, Jerome, Undated (Box 22, Folder 46)
  - Kopf, Frank A., Undated (Box 22, Folder 47)
  - Kopka, Lynn M., Undated (Box 22, Folder 48)
  - Kopka, Lynn M., Undated (Box 22, Folder 49)
  - Koplow, Amy H., Undated (Box 22, Folder 50)
  - Kopp, Steve, Undated (Box 22, Folder 51)
  - Kopp, Rick, Undated (Box 22, Folder 52)
  - Korenblum, Boris, Undated (Box 22, Folder 53)
  - Korenblum, Boris, Undated (Box 22, Folder 54)
  - Koseloff, Valerian F., Undated (Box 22, Folder 55)
  - Koslowski, Rey, Undated (Box 22, Folder 56)
  - Kotval, Jeroo S., Undated (Box 22, Folder 57)
  - Kotval, Jeroo S., Undated (Box 22, Folder 58)
  - Kouba, Vicky, Undated (Box 22, Folder 59)
  - Kowalchyk, John J., Undated (Box 22, Folder 60)
  - Krahn, Mary L., Undated (Box 22, Folder 61)
  - Kranich, Laurence Joel, Undated (Box 22, Folder 62)
  - Krantz, Douglas K., Undated (Box 22, Folder 63)
  - Kraus, William, Undated (Box 22, Folder 64)
  - Kraus, William C., Undated (Box 22, Folder 65)
  - Krause, Jo Ann, Undated (Box 22, Folder 66)
  - Krege, George W., Undated (Box 22, Folder 67)
  - Kress, Jack, Undated (Box 22, Folder 68)
  - Kriger, Mark P., Undated (Box 22, Folder 69)
  - Kressner, Herbert W., Undated (Box 22, Folder 70)
  - Krohn, Marvin, Undated (Box 22, Folder 71)
  - Krone, William, Undated (Box 22, Folder 72)
  - Krosby, H. Peter, Undated (Box 22, Folder 73)
  - Krosby, H. Peter, Undated (Box 22, Folder 74)
  - Krull, Robert, Undated (Box 22, Folder 75)
  - Kruzan, O. Charles, Undated (Box 22, Folder 76)
  - Krykowski, Linda, Undated (Box 22, Folder 77)
  - Krzykowski, Linda M., 1993 (Box 22, Folder 78)
  - Kuemzli, Alfred, Undated (Box 22, Folder 79)
  - Kuernan, Peter, Undated (Box 22, Folder 80)
  - Kuethe, James L., Undated (Box 22, Folder 81)
  - Kujawski, Ronald F., Undated (Box 22, Folder 82)
  - Kuivila, Henry G., Undated (Box 22, Folder 83)
  - Kuivila, Henry G., Undated (Box 22, Folder 84)
  - Kulikowski, Robert R., Undated (Box 22, Folder 85)
  - Kumar-Tayi, Giri, Undated (Box 22, Folder 86)
  - Kupferberg, Audrey, Undated (Box 22, Folder 87)
  - Kupic, Mary, Undated (Box 22, Folder 88)
  - Kuritz, Hyman, Undated (Box 22, Folder 89)
  - Kurland, Norman, Undated (Box 22, Folder 90)
  - Kusick, Colman F., Undated (Box 22, Folder 91)
  - Kuusisto, Alan A., Undated (Box 22, Folder 92)
  - Kuusisto, Alan A., Undated (Box 22, Folder 93)
  - Kuusisto, Alan A., Undated (Box 22, Folder 94)
  - Kuusisto, Alan A., Undated (Box 22, Folder 95)
  - Kuzn, I. Chen, Undated (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Kuznetsov, Igor, Undated (Box 23, Folder 2)
- L, 1851-2005; 12
  - La Fond, Deborah, 1995 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Labella, Vincent, Undated (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - LaCroix, Mina B., Undated (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Lachmann, Richard, Undated (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Lachmann, Richard, Undated (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Lackman, Abraham, Undated (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Lagory, Mark, Undated (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Laferriere, Alaina, Undated (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - LaFlure, Spencer C., Undated (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Lahiri, Kajal (also R. Hamilton Lankford), Undated (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Lahiri, Kajal, Undated (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Lahiri, Kajal, Undated (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Lala, G. Garland, Undated (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - LaManna, Michael, Undated (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - LaManna, Michael, Undated (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Lamb, Sandra, Undated (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Lamkin, Donna S., Undated (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Lampman, Nathalie "Lee", Undated (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Lance, Timothy, Undated (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Lance, Tim, Undated (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Landin, Mike, Undated (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Landin, Michael, Undated (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Landin, Michael, Undated (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Landsberg, Dennis R., Undated (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - Landsman, Gail, Undated (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - Lane, James A., Undated (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - Lane, Robyn, Undated (Box 23, Folder 29)
  - Lanford, Oscar E., Undated (Box 23, Folder 30)
  - Lanford, William A., Undated (Box 23, Folder 31)
  - Lang, Berel, Undated (Box 23, Folder 32)
  - Lang, Varley, Undated (Box 23, Folder 33)
  - Langer, Judith, Undated (Box 23, Folder 34)
  - Langer, Judith (also Arthur Applebee), Undated (Box 23, Folder 35)
  - Lanier, Charles, Undated (Box 23, Folder 36)
  - Lanier, Charles, Undated (Box 23, Folder 37)
  - Lankford, R. Hamilton, Undated (Box 23, Folder 38)
  - Lankowski, Carl F., Undated (Box 23, Folder 39)
  - Lanni, Robert P., Undated (Box 23, Folder 40)
  - Lapenis, Adrei, Undated (Box 23, Folder 41)
  - Lapinski, Leonard, Undated (Box 23, Folder 42)
  - Larkin, T.J., Undated (Box 23, Folder 43)
  - Larney, Violet H., Undated (Box 23, Folder 44)
  - Larney, Violet Hachmeister, Undated (Box 23, Folder 45)
  - Larson, Emil L., Undated (Box 23, Folder 46)
  - Larwood, Laurie, Undated (Box 23, Folder 47)
  - Laskey, Robert E., Undated (Box 23, Folder 48)
  - Latta, Anne, Undated (Box 23, Folder 49)
  - Latta, Jacqueline, Undated (Box 23, Folder 50)
  - Lauenstein, Cecilia, Undated (Box 23, Folder 51)
  - Laurenzi, Bernard, Undated (Box 23, Folder 52)
  - Lavallce, Anne M., Undated (Box 23, Folder 53)
  - Law, Thomas, Undated (Box 23, Folder 54)
  - Lawrence, Carlyle, Undated (Box 23, Folder 55)
  - Lawrence, Charles E., Undated (Box 23, Folder 56)
  - Briar-Lawson, Katharine, Undated (Box 23, Folder 57)
  - Lawson, Hal A., Undated (Box 23, Folder 58)
  - Lawson, Raef, Undated (Box 23, Folder 59)
  - Layton, Donald, Undated (Box 23, Folder 60)
  - Lazic, Margarita, Undated (Box 23, Folder 61)
  - LeBurn, Fred, Undated (Box 23, Folder 62)
  - LeComte, Edward S., Undated (Box 23, Folder 63)
  - LeComte, Edward, Undated (Box 23, Folder 64)
  - Lederman, Norman, Undated (Box 23, Folder 65)
  - Lednev, Igor K., Undated (Box 23, Folder 66)
  - Lee, Amy, Undated (Box 23, Folder 67)
  - Lee, Eunju, Undated (Box 23, Folder 68)
  - Lee, Hak C., Undated (Box 23, Folder 69)
  - Lee, Joon Koo, Undated (Box 23, Folder 70)
  - Lee, Min-Ho, Undated (Box 23, Folder 71)
  - Lee, Pong S., Undated (Box 23, Folder 72)
  - Lee, Seung Ho, Undated (Box 23, Folder 73)
  - Lee, Susane, Undated (Box 23, Folder 74)
  - Lee, Tae M, 1966 (Box 23, Folder 75)
  - Lee, Taesul (Mr.), Undated (Box 23, Folder 76)
  - Lees, Francis C., Undated (Box 23, Folder 77)
  - Lees, Patricia L, Undated (Box 23, Folder 78)
  - Leese, Joseph, Undated (Box 23, Folder 79)
  - Leese, Joseph, Undated (Box 23, Folder 80)
  - Lewandowski, Cathleen, Undated (Box 23, Folder 81)
  - Le Fevre, Henry F., Undated (Box 23, Folder 82)
  - Lehan, Edward A., Undated (Box 23, Folder 83)
  - Lehman, Amy, Undated (Box 23, Folder 84)